<resources>
    <string name="tfe_ic_app_name" translation_description="Image Classification demo app [CHAR_LIMIT=40]">TFL Classify</string>
    <string name="tfe_ic_camera_error" translation_description="Error regarding camera support[CHAR_LIMIT=40]">This device doesn\'t support Camera2 API.</string>
    <string name="tfe_ic_model" translatable="false">Model:</string>
    <string-array name="tfe_ic_models" translatable="false">
        <item>Quantized</item>
        <item>Float</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="tfe_ic_device" translatable="false">Device:</string>
    <string-array name="tfe_ic_devices" translatable="false">
        <item>CPU</item>
        <item>GPU</item>
        <item>NNAPI</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="app_name">OTN(V-1.0)</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Preference Titles -->
    <string name="messages_header">Messages</string>
    <string name="sync_header">Sync</string>

    <!-- Messages Preferences -->
    <string name="signature_title">Your signature</string>
    <string name="reply_title">Default reply action</string>

    <!-- Sync Preferences -->
    <string name="sync_title">Sync email periodically</string>
    <string name="attachment_title">Download incoming attachments</string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_on">Automatically download attachments for incoming emails
    </string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_off">Only download attachments when manually requested</string>
    <string name="return_home">return home</string>

    <string name="label_google_sign_in">Firebase + Google Sign In</string>
    <string name="desc_google_sign_in">Use a Google Sign In credential to authenticate with Firebase.</string>

    <string name="label_facebook_login">Firebase + Facebook Login</string>
    <string name="desc_facebook_login">Use a Facebook Login credential to authenticate with Firebase.</string>

    <string name="label_emailpassword">Email/Password Authentication</string>
    <string name="desc_emailpassword">Use an email and password to authenticate with Firebase.</string>

    <string name="label_passwordless">Passwordless Authentication</string>
    <string name="desc_passwordless">Use only an email to authenticate with Firebase.</string>

    <string name="label_phone_auth">Phone Number Authentication</string>
    <string name="desc_phone_auth">Use a phone number to authenticate with Firebase.</string>

    <string name="label_anonymous_auth">Anonymous Authentication</string>
    <string name="desc_anonymous_auth">Sign in anonymously and then later upgrade to a full Firebase Auth user.</string>

    <string name="label_custom_auth">Custom Authentication</string>
    <string name="desc_custom_auth">Use a custom token signed by your own server to authenticate with Firebase.</string>

    <string name="label_firebase_ui">FirebaseUI Auth</string>
    <string name="desc_firebase_ui">Use the FirebaseUI-Android library to authenticate with Firebase.</string>

    <string name="label_generic_idp">Generic OAuth</string>
    <string name="desc_generic_idp">Use a generic OAuth identity provider, like Apple, Microsoft, Yahoo, or Twitter to authenticate with Firebase.</string>

    <string name="label_multi_factor">Multi-Factor Authentication</string>
    <string name="desc_multi_factor">Use SMS for two-factor authentication. Note: this feature is only available for Cloud Identity Platform.</string>

    <string name="hint_user_id">User ID</string>
    <string name="get_custom_token">Get Token</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="create_account">Create Account</string>
    <string name="send_link">Send Link</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="verify_email">Verify</string>
    <string name="disconnect">Disconnect</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading…</string>
    <string name="custom_token">Custom Token</string>
    <string name="signed_in">Signed In</string>
    <string name="signed_out">Signed Out</string>
    <string name="token_null">Token: null</string>
    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="desc_firebase_lockup">Firebase logo and name</string>
    <string name="auth_failed">Authentication failed</string>
    <string name="start_phone_auth">Start</string>
    <string name="verify_phone_auth">Verify</string>
    <string name="resend_phone_auth">Resend</string>
    <string name="hint_phone_number">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="hint_verification_code">Verification Code</string>
    <string name="status_code_sent">Code Sent</string>
    <string name="status_verification_failed">Verification failed</string>
    <string name="status_verification_succeeded">Verification succeeded</string>
    <string name="status_sign_in_failed">Sign-in failed</string>
    <string name="instant_validation">(instant validation)</string>

    <string name="firebase_status_fmt">Firebase UID: %s</string>
    <string name="firebase_user_management">Firebase User Management</string>

    <string name="google_status_fmt">Google User: %s</string>
    <string name="google_title_text">Google Sign In</string>

    <string name="facebook_status_fmt">Facebook User: %s</string>
    <string name="facebook_title_text">Facebook Login</string>

    <string name="emailpassword_status_fmt">Email User: %1$s (verified: %2$b)</string>
    <string name="emailpassword_title_text">Email and Password</string>

    <string name="passwordless_status_fmt">Email User: %1$s (verified: %2$b)</string>
    <string name="passwordless_title_text">Passwordless Sign In</string>
    <string name="status_email_not_sent">Send link to your email to get started.</string>
    <string name="status_email_sent">Link sent, check your email to continue.</string>
    <string name="status_link_found">Link received, enter email to sign in.</string>

    <string name="phone_title_text">Phone Number</string>

    <string name="twitter_status_fmt">Twitter User: %s</string>
    <string name="twitter_title_text">Twitter Login</string>

    <string name="firebaseui_status_fmt">Firebase User: %s</string>
    <string name="firebaseui_title_text">FirebaseUI Auth</string>

    <string name="generic_title_text">OAuth Sign In</string>
    <string name="generic_signin_fmt">Sign In with %s</string>
    <string name="generic_status_fmt">User: %s (%s)</string>
    <string name="generic_label_provider">Provider:</string>

    <string name="id_fmt">User ID: %s</string>
    <string name="email_fmt">Email: %s</string>

    <string name="enroll_mfa">Enroll MFA</string>
    <string name="unenroll_mfa">Unenroll MFA</string>
    <string name="reload">Reload</string>

    <string name="custom_auth_signin_status_user">User ID: %s</string>
    <string name="custom_auth_signin_status_failed">Error: sign in failed</string>

    <string name="error_sign_in_failed">Sign in failed, see logs for details.</string>
    <string name="multi_factor_signed_out">You are not signed in. To use this sample, first navigate to the Email/Password example to sign in and then return here to enroll in multi-factor auth.</string>


    <string name="squirrelText">Squirrels are generally small animals, ranging a size of 10–14 cm (3.9–5.5 in) in total length and just 12–26 g (0.42–0.92 oz) in weight, to up to 1.27 m (4 ft 2 in) in total length, and up to 8 kg (18 lb) or more in weight. Squirrels typically have slender bodies with bushy tails and large eyes. In general, their fur is soft and silky, though much thicker in some species than others. The dimensions can vary depending on the type squirrel. They are not dangerous to the human, they would rather run than fight.</string>
    <string name="spiderText">Spiders are found worldwide on every continent except for Antarctica, and have become established in nearly every habitat with the exceptions of air and sea colonization. As of July 2019, at least 48,200 spider species, and 120 families have been recorded by taxonomists. Spiders are predators, mostly eating insects and other spiders, although a few large species also hunt birds and lizards. Spiders use a wide range of strategies to capture prey: trapping it in sticky webs, lassoing it with sticky bolas, mimicking the prey to avoid detection, or running it down. Most detect prey mainly by sensing vibrations, but the active hunters have acute vision. Depending on the type some of them can be dangerous to humans, mainly because of the venom. Even though the spider uses its venom to protect itself, it can be used to endanger people. Although only a few spiders produce worse bites than a mosquito, avoid if possible. If you have been bitten search immediate medical help. </string>
    <string name="dogText">The dog is the predecessor to the extant gray wolf, but modern wolves are not closely related to the wolves that were first domesticated, which implies that the direct ancestor of the dog is extinct. The dog was the first species to be domesticated and has been selectively bred over millennia for various behaviors, sensory capabilities, and physical attributes. Their long association with humans has led dogs to be uniquely attuned to human behavior. Dogs vary widely in shape, size and colors. They perform many roles for humans, such as hunting, herding, pulling loads, protection, assisting police and military, companionship and, more recently, aiding disabled people and therapeutic roles. This influence on human society has given them the sobriquet of "man's best friend".</string>
    <string name="catText">The cat is a domestic species of small carnivorous mammal. It is the only domesticated species in the family Felidae and is often referred to as the domestic cat to distinguish it from the wild members of the family. Domestic cats are valued by humans for companionship and their ability to hunt pests such as rodents. About 60 cat breeds are recognized by various cat registries. The cat is similar in anatomy to the other Felid species: it has a strong flexible body, quick reflexes, sharp teeth and retractable claws adapted to killing small prey. Its night vision and sense of smell are well developed. Cat communication includes vocalizations like meowing, purring, trilling, hissing, growling and grunting as well as cat-specific body language. It is a solitary hunter but a social species. It can hear sounds too faint or too high in frequency for human ears, such as those made by mice and other small mammals. It is a predator that is most active at dawn and dusk.</string>
    <string name="butterflyText">Butterflies have the typical four-stage insect life cycle. Winged adults lay eggs on the food plant on which their larvae, known as caterpillars, will feed. The caterpillars grow, sometimes very rapidly, and when fully developed, pupate in a chrysalis. When metamorphosis is complete, the pupal skin splits, the adult insect climbs out, and after its wings have expanded and dried, it flies off. Some butterflies, especially in the tropics, have several generations in a year, while others have a single generation, and a few in cold locations may take several years to pass through their entire life cycle. Butterflies are often polymorphic, and many species make use of camouflage, mimicry and aposematism to evade their predators. Some, like the monarch and the painted lady, migrate over long distances. Many butterflies are attacked by parasites or parasitoids, including wasps, protozoans, flies, and other invertebrates, or are preyed upon by other organisms. Some species are pests because in their larval stages they can damage domestic crops or trees; other species are agents of pollination of some plants. Larvae of a few butterflies (e.g., harvesters) eat harmful insects, and a few are predators of ants, while others live as mutualists in association with ants.</string>

    <string-array name="DBCategories">
        <item>Animals</item>
        <item>Plants</item>
        <item>Mushrooms</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
